[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "Has it a little bit of sex drugs and rock and roll?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "My life is -- is a bit crazy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "I don't care what it takes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "I didn't at all that I was going to be a star.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "I mean, how do you create that kind of aura when by nature you're not really like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "What are the values do you think that she's instilled in you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, definitely that, you know, beauty fades and who you are from within is forever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "When does she -- since you became famous, successful, when has she been the most angry with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "I remember when we first had our single on the radio and I was starting to feel like I was hot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "you've never sung again like that in a store with your mom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "EYONCE: No, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "DT", "JJ", "''", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "What is the moment for your mom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "I can say probably when I sang \"the last\" for the president.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Doesn't it sound amazing when you say things like that now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "How old were you when that happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "I was 21.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "What effect did that have on you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "It had a very deep effect on me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "So, when you had this time with him and he knew he was dying, do you think because he realized he wasn't going to be around this was the last chance to have that conversation with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "I think he honestly had a spiritual awakening because he, you know -- and I don't want to paint him as this, you know, horrible man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "What did he say to you when he finally opened up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "I have two sisters from my father's first marriage, and he apologized to all of us, told us how much he loved us, which was a very emotional moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "But do you dream, you know wishfully, of getting married, having more children --?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "VBG", "JJR", "NNS", ":", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "That more conventional thing that your mother certainly dreamed of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "But, what went wrong then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Young.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Too young?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Young, a lot going on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"]}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "If I was interviewing Zoe about you, how do you think she would describe you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "I think she would say that I'm extremely funny and goofy and the opposite of everything you said today about being cool and all that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bahamas"]}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "How are you spending the Christmas holidays?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "I am going to go to the Bahamas.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Do you do all that kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Do you sing Christmas carols?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "No, I know the tunes, but no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Goofy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "If it's your sister, can you completely trust each other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marie"]}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "What's the thing that takes you to that level?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "I don't know if I speak on behalf of Marie, but when we put the show together, you can throw as much money you want at a show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Who of all the greats that have played in Vegas would you like to seen in the face of others?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "We did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "You saw them all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "We worked with them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Did you perform with Sinatra?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sinatra"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Sammy Davis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sammy Davis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Dean Martin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "ORGAN: Elvis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "What else made those guys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "They worked.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Do you remember what Groucho Marx did now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Groucho Marx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "He was the (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "So, this was completely inappropriate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "-- which would have been illegal nowadays.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Wayne"]}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "What was John Wayne like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "John Wayne was a very stoic man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Wayne"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "How do you find America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "OWNEY: I love America.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Have we lost our way a bit, you think, globally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "I think that we have lost our way a little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Who do you think is the boss?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "I know who the boss is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Listen, you know, behind every great man, there's a greater woman, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Tell me about the project.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "How are you spending Christmas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Well, we're spending Christmas with our kids.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Christmas turkey and all the trimmings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Christmas turkey, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Brussels"]}, "docId": "111224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Brussels sprouts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "I love Brussels sprouts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]